Lee Adamson

+65 8360 1900

lee.adamson@mac.com

www.iamlee.co.uk



Profile

I am a keen web development professional seeking a new challenge, I have spent the past 7 years at Jack Wills (www.jackwills.com), a London based fashion retailer. I have been a part of every digital step that Jack Wills has taken over the years, with various websites and micro-sites. Over the years I feel I have gained important experience within the e-commerce ecosystem and pressures associated with the fast paced nature of online fashion. The main Jack Wills sites have seen many forms over the years, we have taken the quite basic html site through an open source CMS integration, Responsive design overhaul, backend systems migrations and most recently a platform migration onto the scaleable commerce platform (Demandware).

<u>www.jackwills.com</u>, <u>blog.jackwills.com</u>, <u>allthingsjack.jackwills.com</u>, <u>www.jackwillsoutlet.com</u> <u>jwseasonnaires.com</u>, <u>jwunsigned.com</u>, <u>aubinandwills.com</u>, <u>aubincinema.com</u>.

Outside of my jack wills work I have also spent time on private projects for a range of clients and sectors not limited to e-commerce.

typestudio.co.uk (Wordpress 1 page site for architect studio), <u>lightalloy.com</u> (marketing site for a rock covers band), <u>telenumbers.co.uk</u> (Wordpress site with e-commerce functionality, woocommerce), <u>funkmartini.gr</u> (mobile specific styling updates and back office feature enhancements)

Experience

AUGUST 2014 - PRESENT

DIGITAL DIRECTOR, APPCAKE LTD, LONDON - SINGAPORE

Working alongside the founder, set up AppCake Ltd, a small development agency whose primary business is MacAssistant RT, a fully featured scout utility for Football Manager 2015. We also have web development clients Type Studio and FunkMartini. The business is progressed in personal time outside of full time working commitments.

FEBRUARY 2013 - PRESENT

SENIOR FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER / TEAM LEAD, JACK WILLS, LONDON, UK

Leading front end team, requirements gathering from stakeholders for various projects, continual improvement of <u>jackwills.com</u>, feature enhancement of CMS for business users. Front End platform migration. Adhering to company wide seasonal strict deadlines utilising SCRUM methodology.

AUGUST 2010 - FEBRUARY 2013

SENIOR FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER, JACK WILLS, LONDON, UK

Working alongside a team of front end developers for further development of the company sites, implementation of an open source <u>ASP.NET</u> CMS, development of a responsive approach for <u>jackwills.com</u>.

MAY 2008 - AUGUST 2010

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER, JACK WILLS, LONDON, UK

Sole responsibility for all front end code for all aspects of jackwills.com Working alongside designer to create <u>aubinandwills.com</u> as a new sister brand to Jack Wills.

APRIL 2008 - MAY 2008

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER (CONTRACT), JACK WILLS, LONDON, UK

HTML email generation, page content updates, site improvements.

MARCH 2008 - APRIL 2008

PRINT/LAYOUT DESIGNER (CONTRACT), POKERSTARS, LONDON, UK

Production of printed assets for global marketing material for poker events, following brand guidelines.

JANUARY 2008 - MARCH 2008

VARIOUS CONTRACT ROLES (CONTRACT), LONDON, UK

Print Design, Layout Design, HTML layout for various clients/agencies on a freelance basis.

FEBRUARY 2005 - DECEMBER 2007

GRAPHIC / WEB DESIGNER, DIGITAL IMAGIN, HITCHIN, UK

Meeting with clients, requirements gathering, concept designs and final delivery of printed and digital assets.

Education

Learning Tree International, London - 2014

Javascript for Modern Web Development (Course 2319) (Exam Score 87.5%)

Learning Tree International, London - 2011

jQuery: A Comprehensive Introduction (Course 1610) (Exam Score 92.5%)

University of Bedfordshire, UK - 2000-2003

Graphic Design & Business Practice BA(Hons) (2:1)

Skills

My technical skills include, but not limited to: HTML5, CSS3 (& LESS + Sass), Responsive Web Design (RWD), JADE, jQuery, Umbraco (Open Source CMS), Bootstrap, XSLT, Wordpress, SVN/TFS/GitHub. Alongside my main skills I have had exposure to <u>ASP.NET</u> MVC, Javascript, PHP. I am also fully versed in the Adobe CS suite including video editing and encoding.

References

Referrals are available upon request.